First of all, if we talk about the market, Nifty
closed at 16025 and today
Nifty has seen a decline of zero point 62 percent
and in this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company
and the market cap of the company is Rs 61,000 740
crore and AP Russia is Rs 4856 and the company
gives dividend of 0.26% and the return of the company is
kept alive 1954 and return on
equity is 15 point 3
and if we talk about the positive points in the company, then the
company has reduced its debt and the
company is almost debt free and the
result of the company is expected to be good in the next quarter
and the
dividend payout of the company is expected to break these points
and if we talk about the negative points, then
in the last two-three years the promoter holding has increased by
783 percent
and now let us also see the profit of the company, it is Rs
1049 crore
1194 crore
1473 crore 1271 crore
and the share holding  If we talk about it, the
promoter's wedding is 48 point zero four
Rafi's old in 12628 six degrees more is
your pocket 73 and public holding 1134
and now if we talk about the company's chart, then today a
rise of 30 percent has been seen
and at this time the price of the share is
₹100 note and at this time RSS
RSS
and this share is
available in subscribe subscribe
if you want to buy in this company then
you
can buy
that this is all in this video if you
liked the information given in the video then
like the video, share it and
subscribe to our channel